翻译，压制: 布尔
字体: 思源黑体 Medium
思源黑体 Bold
故乡的路 带我回家吧
Country roads take me home
回到我期盼已久的归宿
To the place I belong
西弗吉尼亚
West virginia
大山母亲
Mountain momma
故乡的路 带我回家吧
Take me home country roads
故乡的路
country roads
西弗吉尼亚 几乎如天堂一般
Almost heaven west virginia
那儿有蓝岭山脉和仙纳度河
Blue ridge mountains shenandoah river
那里的生命比树木更久远
Life is old there older than the trees
但比那山脉年轻
Younger than the mountains
像微风一样生长
Growin like a breeze
故乡的路 带我回家吧
Country roads take me home
回到我期盼已久的归宿
To the place I belong
西弗吉尼亚
West virginia
大山母亲
Mountain momma
带我回家吧 故乡的路
Take me home country roads
故乡的路
country roads
清晨我听见她的声音在对我呼唤
I hear her voice in the morning hours she calls me
收音机里的声音让我想起了遥远的家
Radio reminds me of my home far away
沿着公路行驶 我感觉
Driving down the road I get a feeling
也许我昨天就该回到家中
that I should have been home
昨天
Yesterday
带我回家吧 故乡的路
Country roads take me home
回到我期盼已久的归宿
To the place I belong
归宿
I belong
西弗吉尼亚
West virginia
大山母亲
Mountain momma
带我回家吧 故乡的路
Take me home country roads
西弗吉尼亚
West virginia
大山母亲
Mountain momma
带我回家吧
Take me home
故乡的路
country roads